Coming here to die? What idiots.
Fighting with you is boring.
Come together.
I don't even know
which is the magic beast.
Song is as strong as a monster too.
It's about done here.
Sung. you've really gotten stronger.
Where did you get that great dagger?
Jinwoo.
I haven't had a chance to heal you today.
Ah... Is it?
I hope you won't need it this time.
No. I'm counting on you.
Just as I thought.
He has changed a lot.
Not just his appearance.
but even his aura.
I can feel his ease and confidence.
Did you learn martial arts?
Let's keep going.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
It's a fork of the road.
This one is even easier than expected.
Should we split up into three groups?
Although it will increase the risk.
we could end the mission sooner.
Let's do that.
I'll take the right path
with those convicts.
If you find the BOSS room.
please inform me immediately.
It must be because
my perception has improved.
From here. I can feel
that the boss is ahead on this path.
I can't earn many points
from fighting goblins.
Mr. Song.
Let's take the left path.
I got it.
Then we'll take the middle one.
Yes.
I can handle goblins of this level.
I hope the mission will end well.
It should.
They brought the weakest hunter.
so the level of this dungeon must be low.
We thought so last time. didn't we?
I've decided.
Once this mission is over.
I will go apologize to Sung.
Eh?
You couldn't forget it either. right?
We ran away.
A man who prides himself
as a hunter ran away.
I did it for my family.
but it doesn't change the fact
that I abandoned my companion.
If I want to continue
claiming to be a hunter.
I must learn to admit my mistakes.
Will he forget us?
He will never forget us.
But I still have to apologize.
Alright. let's go.
Too weak.
Goblins are no match at all.
Finished them all?
It's a piece of cake.
I'm not even satisfied.
What if they were humans?
What?
Can you do the same?
Humans aren't that different
from these magic beasts.
Yeah. they're all the same.
What do you want from me?
Three men violated my daughter.
She hanged herself.
My wife ended up in a mental
hospital due to the trauma.
But those three guys
will be released in a few years
as if nothing had happened.
And they...
They still have their hunter licenses.
I've heard that
hunters can get sentence reductions
by participating in raid missions.
It's not fair at all.
My daughter will never return to me.
What is that?
Here's three billion.
Please
Kill them for me.
No outsider would know what
happened in the dungeon. right?
I beg you.
Please help me.
After leaving here. I'll report to
the Surveillance Department
that the three of you
encountered a hundred goblins here.
This path is really winding.
Are we really going forward?
Did we choose the wrong path?
Phew.
Help...
Don't expect a quick death.
I'll torture you as much as possible
before ending your lives.
That's what I was told to do.
What... what are you doing?
Ah.
The paths are connected?
In other words.
the left path leads to the BOSS room.
That saves me the time for finding it.
Help me...
Although this went
differently than planned...
That Kang Taeshik.
He and his superior from the Surveillance
Department visited me at the hospital.
I hope he doesn't remember me.
Mr. Song.
Okay.
What happened?
Jungho.
Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kim.
Joohee... treat them.
Go treat them!
Yes!
Mr. Kim. pull yourself together.
These wounds were not
caused by magic beasts.
They are caused by sharp blades.
Moreover.
the enemy avoided lethal injuries
to create more wounds.
It's no use.
I can't survive.
What nonsense is that?
You need to be alive.
Don't you have a family?
You must...
You must live no matter what!
Only then can I hate you.
I'm sorry.
I am truly sorry.
I didn't want to apologize like this.
I want to bow my head
and apologize to you.
Sung.
I am really sorry.
Believe me.
Kim.
Wow.
You're quite agile.
I wanted to take care of the healer first.
I didn't expect that move to be blocked.
Mr. Kang.
Did you do this?
What if I did?
Aren't you from the Hunter's Association?
How could you do this?
I've thought of a good story.
I was going to claim that
you were killed by goblins.
But I want to make a change.
These criminals attempted to escape.
They killed you first.
and ambushed me from behind
when I fought the Boss.
However. with their strength.
they couldn't harm me.
In the end. only I survived.
Perfect. isn't it?
You scum.
You can't defeat him.
Let me do it.
Kim. lend me your sword.
It's been a long time since
I've crossed swords with someone.
He is B-rank. higher than me.
But...
Joohee. can you cast a physical
enhancement spell on me?
Yes.
Assassins usually have low defense.
and that's their weakness.
I must target that.
Even if an old Mage had
his strength enhanced.
it would only backfire.
Right now. I am a swordsman.
You are a Mage.
What's the point of picking up a sword?
There might be a point.
You have good skills.
Although enhanced.
your movements are
very skilled in themselves.
Although just for a moment.
Mr. Song caught up to his speed.
If he could be a bit faster...
Your attack is fast and accurate.
You have the ability to attack
with a sword instead of magic.
But that's all there is to it.
That healer is annoying.
I should get rid of you first.
Turning your back on a swordsman?
Seems like you're no ordinary old man.
After all. I am the master
of an S-rank hunter.
In terms of swordsmanship.
I won't lose to you.
That being said.
the power you've been granted
is ultimately limited.
A Mage
can never keep up with an Assassin.
Mr. Song.
No.
The healer has exhausted her power.
It's over.
Did it work?
You posed as a swordsman
to lower my guard against the magic.
You unleashed a magical attack
at the moment I made my final strike.
This tactic isn't bad.
You cunning old fox.
Is it over?
Die.
You again.
Who are you?
I'm Sung Jinwoo.
an E-Rank hunter.
E-rank?
How is that possible?
Sung.
What was that just now?
If you are a power-type E-rank hunter.
that strength would make sense.
But you reacted fast enough
to block my attacks twice.
Are you an Assassin?
Never mind. It doesn't matter.
You've been hiding your true power. right?
You seem to know each other.
Then you can't be a False Ranker.
After all. you wouldn't
leave any witnesses alive.
In that case.
there's only one answer.
You're a second awakener.
Sung is...
A second awakener.
If that's the case.
did it happen after
the double dungeon incident?
Double dungeon?
Is he
that lousy E-rank hunter?
His appearance and impression
are completely different.
And his measured value was only 10.
Did the second awakening
happen after that?
If so.
how did he survive the double dungeon?
Well. regardless.
it seems you have little
experience as a hunter.
Let me teach you a thing or two.
Why do you do this?
You mean these prisoners?
I was entrusted
by the family of the victim.
They killed someone without any remorse.
I'm doing justice.
No. I mean Mr. Kim and Mr. Kang.
Why did you kill them?
Was it to silence them?
Then you could have made it quick.
Yet you avoided inflicting fatal wounds.
as if to torture them.
It's for the victim?
Cut it out.
That is not your true nature.
Yes.
These things are trivial for me.
But you seem to have misunderstood.
I am a B-rank hunter that
many large guilds fight for.
Why do you think
I joined Hunter's Association
that pays a meager salary?
Because
compared to killing magic beasts.
I enjoy killing people more.
Even with a second awakening.
an E-rank hunter can't be very strong.
You're too slow.
You're quite fast.
How can he have such skills?
He's no longer the Sung I knew.
Our speeds are comparable.
Even if we have the same skills
and the same strength.
your experience
against high-level opponents
is far too little compared to mine.
These differences will
lead to your defeat.
You are a tough one.
-Excuse me.
-What?
Could you please tone
down your killing intent?
Look.
The system has responded to you.
Now I have to thank this system.
It has given me another reason
why I must kill you.
System?
What's up with him?
I'm the one with the upper hand.
He got even faster.
It's poison.
Is this a special effect of your dagger?
Then let me show you
something interesting too.
He disappeared.
I had completely concealed my presence.
Your senses are sharp.
Skill Invisibility.
It hides one's shape. sound.
scent. among others.
Even among Assassins.
only a very few can acquire this skill.
Of course. those who know
that I can use this skill
are nonexistent.
After all.
there hasn't been one
who has seen me use this skill
and lived to tell about it.
I have sealed your speed.
-Jinwoo.
-Stay put.
After I kill him. it's your turn.
If this goes on. Sung...
With your foot injured.
can you still dodge my attacks?
Hey.
Have you said enough?
Full Recovery.
He recovered instantly.
A Fighter capable of using healing magic.
I've never heard of such a thing.
How many times can he use it?
I cannot predict it at all.
He's a dangerous one.
I've lost another emotion.
With scum like you.
is it a waste of time to get angry?
I see.
You've done it. right?
You're like me after all.
I see.
He probably had to make
many difficult choices in a short time.
It isn't just his appearance that changed.
Awakening.
This power beyond common sense
has changed the rules of the world.
This is a lawless land
belonging only to hunters.
There is no law here.
only the winner.
Can he be
gauging my position
through my killing intent?
But even so. he still can't
pinpoint my exact location.
What... what's wrong?
Wait.
No way.
How... is it possible?
You asked me why I killed. right?
It's pointless to apply
ordinary people's views
to hunters who frequently
consort with death.
You're the same.
We've both become killing machines.
So.
I lost and will die.
It's the logical rule.
Who are you?
Being an Assassin.
you are capable of using healing magic
and debuff magic.
I've never heard of that.
Well.
I would like to know too.
Since you've killed me.
you can no longer hide your identity.
What if I were the kind of hunter
who grows constantly in battle?
Your shadow
is already connected to the darkness.
Your power will become
as unfathomable as it.
However. you must be careful.
When you stare into the abyss.
the abyss stares back at you.
Indeed.
My strength has grown rapidly.
But I feel
that as my strength grows.
a part of me is gradually falling apart.
Jinwoo.
Thank you.
You saved us.
Without you. we would have died.
It's nothing.
Please go ahead and leave.
I need to close up the dungeon.
What?
You're going alone?
No. we'll do as you say.
It's a pity that we can't
bury Kim and Kang.
I'll wait for you outside.
Chief Woo.
I've heard the report.
Where are the survivors?
Over there.
Speaking of which.
I didn't expect Kang Taeshik
to be involved in murders.
although I did suspect him.
As his superior. I was too careless.
It's these three.
I remember
he was that E-rank hunter back then.
He looks like a different person.
Long time no see.
Um. you're from
the Surveillance Department.
Woo Jinchul.
This time my subordinate
has caused huge trouble.
But first.
let me get straight to the point.
Which of you
killed Kang Taeshik?
It seems I can no longer hide.
It's a pity.
My collaboration with Jinho
might have to come to an end.
It was me.
I killed Mr. Kang.
Excuse me. I remember your rank is...
I'm a C-rank hunter.
How could a C-rank hunter
manage to kill a B-rank hunter?
Because we have her.
I see.
So you managed to defeat him
with the healer's assistance.
Kang Taeshik was among
the top of the B-rank hunters.
I don't think
a C-rank Mage could kill him.
no matter how hard he tried.
I understand.
We need to complete the report.
Please come with me.
Now is not the time to be smug
about having killed Kang Taeshik.
I couldn't see it at that time.
This person is an A-rank hunter.
He's not someone I can handle right now.
Was I meddling too much?
You must have your reasons
for hiding your strength.
Alright. Consider it my way of
repaying you for saving my life.
Three hours later.
the man who commissioned Kang Taeshik
to kill the prisoners turned himself in.
The whole case was concluded
as legitimate self-defense.
That was exhausting.
Jinwoo.
Do you
remember this?
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-